<pkmkdoc spec="1.12"><properties><title>Neurospaces Developer</title><build>/Users/Abominous/neurospaces_project/developer/source/snapshots/0/OSX_BUILD/Developer.pkg</build><organization>neurospaces.developer</organization><userSees ui="easy"/><min-target os="3"/><domain system="true"/></properties><distribution><versions min-spec="1.000000"/><scripts></scripts></distribution><description>The Neurospaces developer package contains essential tools for Neurospaces development. The Neurospaces project develops software components of neuronal simulator that integrate in a just-in-time manner for the exploration, simulation and validation of accurate neuronal models. Neurospaces spans the range from single molecules to subcellular networks, over single cells to neuronal networks.  Neurospaces is backwards-compatible with the GENESIS simulator, integrates with Python and Perl, separates models from experimental protocols, and reads model definitions from declarative specifications in a variety of formats. This package contains utilities requires for Neurospaces development.</description><contents><choice title="Package_Root" id="choice0" starts_selected="true" starts_enabled="true" starts_hidden="false"><pkgref id="neurospaces.developer.pkg"/></choice></contents><resources bg-scale="none" bg-align="topleft"><locale lang="en"><resource relative="true" mod="true" type="license">../../OSX_BUILD/Resources/License.rtf</resource><resource relative="true" mod="true" type="welcome">../../OSX_BUILD/Resources/Welcome.rtf</resource><resource mime-type="text/rtf" kind="embedded" type="conclusion"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf949\cocoasubrtf540
{\fonttbl\f0\fnil\fcharset0 LucidaGrande;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;}
\pard\tx560\tx1120\tx1680\tx2240\tx2800\tx3360\tx3920\tx4480\tx5040\tx5600\tx6160\tx6720\ql\qnatural\pardirnatural

\f0\fs26 \cf0 The Neurospaces Developer package has been installed on your machine. Make sure that "/usr/local/bin" is in your path so you can call the developer tools from the command line. }]]></resource></locale></resources><requirements><requirement id="file" operator="eq" value="true"><file>/usr/bin/perl</file><message-title>Perl is not installed</message-title><message>Standard Perl for Mac OSX is not installed. Installed this from your Mac OSX installation disks since non-standard perl may cause errors. </message></requirement></requirements><flags/><item type="file">01package.xml</item><mod>properties.title</mod><mod>description</mod><mod>properties.anywhereDomain</mod><mod>properties.systemDomain</mod></pkmkdoc>